Finding aid for the Hollywood Park records LSC.2254
UCLA Library Special Collections
Hollywood Park records
1928-2009
UCLA Library Special Collections
Hollywood Park Operating Company
LSC.2254
364 linear feet (5 boxes, 104 shoe boxes, 189 cartons, 86 flat boxes, 117 oversize flat boxes)
236 audiovisual carriers (236 open reel videotapes)
1 born-digital carriers (1 optical disc)
58 linear feet (12 unprocessed record cartons, 5 unprocessed oversize boxes, 1 unprocessed shoe box, 236 unprocessed reel containers)
The Hollywood Turf Club, later renamed Hollywood Park, opened in 1938. Known as the Track of the Lakes and Flowers, it served as home for a number of talented jockeys, trainers, and prominent thoroughbreds. The collection consists of minute books and ledgers; stock certificate books; scrapbooks; negatives; press clippings; and chart books.
Conditions on Access
Portions of this collection are closed.
Box 312 is restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed to UCLA Library Special Collections.
Many scrapbooks are in fragile condition due to clippings and/or photographs falling off pages.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Hollywood Park Racing Association, 2014.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9978574523606533
Biography/History
The Hollywood Turf Club (later renamed Hollywood Park), opened on June 10, 1938. Constructed on close to 315 acres, it was built to accommodate 30,000 people and 1,250 horses. The race track itself was an oval one mile distance and 90 feet wide.
A year earlier, in 1937, the Los Angeles Times reported that there were two applications for a Los Angeles horse racing track: one submitted by the Golden State Jockey Club, the other from the Hollywood Racing Association. Ultimately the Golden State group was awarded a provisional permit to build. Golden State changed its name to the Hollywood Turf Club and selected a West Los Angeles location near the intersection of Sawtelle and National to build the track. Although granted a provisional permit from the California Horse Racing Board and approval from the Los Angeles Planning Commission to begin building in September 1936, there were "floods of protest" from the West Los Angeles community that led the Hollywood Turf Club to withdraw its application for zoning in West Los Angeles and select the Inglewood location that would be the home of Hollywood Park.
In January 1938, Hollywood Turf Club officers and directors included Hollywood industry figures and Los Angeles businessmen such as Walter McCarty (Beverly Wilshire Hotel), Jack Warner (Warner Bros), Earl Gilmore (Gilmore Oil Company), J. I. Schnitzer (Western Costume Company), Raoul Walsh (motion picture director), Roy Wilcox, Al Jolson (radio artist), C. M. Rood (oil operator), James Duffy (Santa Fe railroad), Thomas Simmons (oil operator), and Alfred Green (motion picture director). According to Jack Warner, the Hollywood Turf Club was to provide another outstanding attraction for visitors and tourists to Southern California.
The infield of the track was beautifully landscaped with lush gardens and small lakes. The Hollywood Park Goose Girl tradition began during the park's first season in 1938. Each year a Goose Girl was chosen and in addition to posing for photographs and making publicity appearances, she would walk among the geese (and other birds) that populated the infield or coast along on the lake in the small boat, the Miz Clementine, feeding the birds. The tradition was discontinued in the 1970s and brought back for a very brief time in the 1990s. In May 1949, less than two weeks before the opening of the track's spring racing season, a fire severely damaged the original grand stand and Club House. The track reopened a little more than a year later in June 1950. Known as the Track of the Lakes and Flowers, Hollywood Park served as home for a number of talented horsemen and eminent thoroughbreds. Among the horses were Seabiscuit, winner of the inaugural Hollywood Gold Cup in 1938, three-time Gold Cup champions Native Diver and Lava Man, Triple Crown winners Citation, Seattle Slew and Affirmed, Great Communicator, Landaluce, and Zenyatta. Jockeys Eddie Arcaro, Jerry Bailey, Jerry Lambert, Donny Longden, Laffit Pincay, Jr., Bill Shoemaker, Mike Smith, Gary Stevens, and George Woolf; and trainers Charlie Whittingham, Barrera Lax, Bob Baffert, and Doug O'Neill also worked at the park. Three legendary horses, Landaluce, Native Diver, and Great Communicator were interned at the race park.
Hollywood Park closed December 22, 2013, ending 75 years of continuous racing in the Southern California region. It was demolished to make way for a residential development.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to Hollywood Park and the California racing community. Included are minute books and ledgers; stock certificate books; scrapbooks; negatives; press clippings; and chart books. The minute books and ledgers represent annual and special meetings of the Hollywood Turf Club and Hollywood Park. The stock certificate books comprise stock certificate sales for the first decade of the track's operation. The scrapbooks and press clippings document media coverage of Hollywood Park, as well as other racetracks such as Santa Anita, Los Alamitos, and the California horse racing culture. The negatives represent Hollywood Park racing seasons and track events. The chart books provide racing statistics regarding horses, jockeys, and odds mostly for the other regional race tracks, with only one chart book representing Hollywood Park.
The collection consists of
Scrapbooks 158 albums (no boxes)
Committee meeting and documented executive-like transactions; Stock certificate books; Thoroughbred magazine (Boxes 1-11 and 17-19)
Chartbooks (Boxes 12-16)
Clippings files (Boxes 20-43)
Negatives (Boxes 44-261)
Bound magazines (Boxes 262-267)
Video Tapes (Boxes 268-294)
Approximately 237 1 inch video tapes (in cases); stored in boxes that measure 22 x 14 x 11 height).
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Minute Books and Ledgers
Series 2: Stock Certificate Books
Series 3: Scrapbooks
Series 4: Negatives
Series 5. Press Clippings
Series 6. Chart Books
Horse racing.; Hollywood Park Operating Company -- Archives
- Minute Books and Ledgers, (1938-1989)
  Restrictions on Access
  Box 312 is restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed to UCLA Library Special Collections.
  Organization and Arrangement
  There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  Scope and Content
  The Minute Books and Ledgers consist of meeting minutes documenting annual and special meetings of the Hollywood Turf Club and Hollywood Park. The bulk of the material represents Executive Committees and Board of Directors' meetings. Additionally represented are a small number of items related to Turf Oil Company, California Turf Foundation Inc., and Prairie Wood Association Inc. In addition to meeting minutes there are a small number of documents related to ownership and incorporation. One California Turf Foundation ledger appears to be mostly doctor, hospital, and medical related entries.
  - California Turf Foundation Inc. Ledger, 1942-1946, 1955 (Box 325)
    Appears to be records of stocks and bonds.
  - The California Turf Foundation, Inc. - ledger, 1948-1954 (Box 312)
    Portions of the contents of this scrapbook are restricted and may be unavailable for use. Inquiries regarding these materials should be directed in writing to the UCLA Library Special Collections.
  - The California Turf Foundation, Inc. - ledger, 1948-1955 (Box 311)
    Appears to be mostly physician, hospital, and medical related entries.
  - Hollywood Turf Club Executive Committee Minutes (Volume I), 1938 Jan-1940 Sept, 1946 Nov-1948 July, 1951 Jan-1964 Sept (Box 315)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Annual Meetings of Shareholders (Volume I), 1938-1970 (Box 314)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume II), 1941 Aug 5 - 1945 May 25 (Box 316)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of the Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume III), 1945 June 4 -1948 Aug 9 (Box 319)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume III), 1948 Aug 30 - 1951 July [6] (Box 320)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume V), 1951 Jan 9 -1956 Nov 7 (Box 318)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume IV), 1951 Sept 12 -1956 Nov 29 (Box 317)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors (Volume IV), 1963 Jan 9 - 1966 Dec 12 (Box 321)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1967 Jan - 1968 Dec (Box 327)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1969 Jan 14 - 1970 Nov 4 (Box 327)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1971 Jan 5 - 1973 Dec 10 (Box 328)
  - Hollywood Park Inc. Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1974 Aug - 1977 Dec (Box 329)
  - Hollywood Park Inc. Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1978 Jan - 1979 Sept (Box 322)
  - Hollywood Park Inc. Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1980 Oct - 1981 Dec (Box 326)
    With a small number of documents related to ownership/incorporation from 1973, 1978, and 1979.
  - Hollywood Park Inc. Minutes of Meetings of the Audit Committee of the Board of Directors, 1973, 1974, 1976, 1977 (Box 330)
  - Hollywood Park Inc. Minutes of Meetings of the Executive Committee, 1974 July - 1977 July (Box 329)
  - Hollywood Park Realty Enterprises, Inc. Minutes of Meetings of Board of Directors, 1981-1984 (Box 331)
  - Hollywood Park Operating Company Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1984 Jan - 1986 Dec (Box 323)
  - Hollywood Park Operating Company Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Directors, 1987 Jan - 1989 Feb (Box 324)
  - Hollywood Park Operating Company and Hollywood Park Realty Enterprises, Inc. Sale of Los Alamitos Race Track Property to Cypress Development, 1989 Nov 20 (Box 331)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Minutes of Meetings of the Shareholders, 1971 Nov - 1976 Feb (Box 328)
  - Prairie Wood Association Inc., 1966 Feb and May 1967 (Box 330)
    Minutes of first meeting and a special meeting of the Board of Directors, Articles of Incorporation, and By-Laws.
  - Turf Oil Company, 1940, 1941, 1945, 1952, 1954, 1956-1959, 1962, 1964 (Box 313)
    Minutes of meetings of Board of Directors, By-Laws, Amendment of Articles of Incorporation (1964).
- Stock Certificate books, (1936-1946)
  The certificate books are arranged in a loose chronological order.
  The series comprises stock certificates representing individual purchasing of stocks, the number of shares purchased, and the date of purchase for the first decade of the track's operation.
  - Hollywood Turf Club 1-150, 1936-1937 (Box 178)
  - Hollywood Turf Club 151-300, 1937 (Box 179)
  - Hollywood Turf Club 1-200, 1937 (Box 180)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1-A200, 1938 (Box 181)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A201-A400, 1938 (Box 182)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A401-A600, 1938 (Box 183)
    With loose folder titled Grant, Cyrus W.; Grant, Ruth C.
  - Hollywood Turf Club A602-A800 (2 volumes), 1938 (Box 184)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A801-A1000 (2 volumes), 1938 (Box 185)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1001-A1202 (2 volumes), 1938 (Box 186)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1203-A1400 (2 volumes), 1938-1939 (Box 187)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1401-1600 (2 volumes), 1939-1940 (Box 188)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1601-A1810 (2 volumes), 1940-1941 (Box 189)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A1811-A2010 (2 volumes), 1941-1942 (Box 190)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A2011-2210 (2 volumes), 1942-1943 (Box 191)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A2211-2410 (2 volumes), 1943-1944 (Box 192)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A2411-2610 (2 volumes), 1944-1945 (Box 193)
  - Hollywood Turf Club A2611-2810 (2 volumes), 1946-1946 (Box 194)
- Scrapbooks, (1938-1993)
  The scrapbooks are arranged in a loose chronological order.
  The Scrapbook albums hold press clippings and/or a small amount of photographs, advertisements, and ephemera about or publicizing Hollywood Park. The press clippings include stories and photographs related to horses and jockeys, horse races, general Hollywood Park advertisements as well as press about park events, personality sightings, and information about other horse racing tracks in the California area. A portion of the scrapbooks are titled to reflect their contents. Unless otherwise noted, the scrapbooks contain press clipping only. Among the various newspapers represented are the Los Angeles Times, the Herald Examiner, the San Diego Evening Tribune, the San Diego Union, the San Francisco Chronicle and San Francisco Examiner.
  - Photographs of Hollywood Turf Club by Floyd Ray, undated (Box 1)
  - Property of Mervyn LeRoy scrapbook, undated (Box 310)
    Photographs mostly featuring horses at Puet starting gate.
  - Scrapbook, undated (Box 85)
    Photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1938 (Box 2, Box 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1938 - 1941 (Box 21)
  - Western Harness Racing Association Meeting, 1938 - 1959 (Box 64)
  - Scrapbooks, 1939 (Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 332)
  - Scrapbook, 1939 July - 1940 Sept (Box 11)
  - Scrapbooks, 1940 (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10)
  - Scrapbooks, 1940 May - July (Box 12, Box 13)
    Clippings and photographs.
  - Scrapbooks, 1941 (Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 22)
  - Scrapbooks, 1944 - 1945 (Box 25, Box 26)
  - Scrapbook, 1945 (Box 27)
  - Hollywood Park 1945 Season: Rings & Finishes Photos (Carroll Photo Service), 1945 Sept - Oct (Box 24)
  - Scrapbook, 1946 (Box 29)
  - Seventh Season 1946 Hollywood Park Advertisements for Mr. Al Wesson from Milton Weinberg Advertising Co. (Box 28)
  - Scrapbooks, 1947 (Box 30, Box 32, Box 33)
  - Horses 1947 Season (Box 31)
  - Scrapbook, circa 1947 (Box 23)
    Photographs only. Horses (mostly identified), some with individuals (some identified), and a small number of photographs documenting the position of horses at various points within a race.
  - Racing Charts, 1947-1948 (Box 310)
  - Scrapbooks, 1948 (Box 35, Box 36, Box 37)
    Box 35: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Ninth Season 1948 Hollywood Park Advertising for Mr. Al Wesson - prepared by Milton Weinberg Advertising Co. (Box 34)
  - Scrapbooks, 1949 (Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 309)
    Box 38: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Hollywood Park 1949 Season (Box 34)
  - Scrapbooks, 1950 (Box 41, Box 42, Box 43)
    Box 42: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1951 (Box 44, Box 45)
    Box 44: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbook, 1951 Aug - 1952 May (Box 47)
  - Scrapbooks, 1952 (Box 46, Box 48)
    Box 46: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1953 (Box 49, Box 50, Box 52)
    Box 49: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1954 (Box 51, Box 53, Box 54)
  - Scrapbook, Santa Anita, 1954 Mar 12 - Apr 8 (Box 309)
  - Scrapbooks, 1955 (Box 55, Box 56)
    Box 55: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1956 (Box 57, Box 58)
    Box 57: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1957 (Box 59, Box 60)
    Box 60: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1958 (Box 61, Box 62)
    Box 61: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1959 (Box 63, Box 64, Box 65)
    Box: 63: Junior League Race Day Hollywood Park Box 64: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbook, 1959 Dec - 1960 July (Box 67)
  - Scrapbook, 1960 (Box 66)
  - Attendance Records for Hollywood Turf Club and Western Harness Racing Inc., 1960-1972 (Box 66)
  - Scrapbooks, 1961 (Box 68, Box 69, Box 70)
    Box 70: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1962 (Box 71, Box 72)
    Box 72: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbook, 1963 (Box 73)
  - Metropolitan Dailies clippings, 1963 (Box 74)
  - Scrapbooks, 1964 (Box 76, Box 77)
    Box 76: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbook, 1965 (Box 79)
  - Metropolitan Dailies clippings, 1965 (Box 78)
  - Operation Department Printed Forms Hollywood Turf Club, 1965 (Box 78)
  - Scrapbook, 1965 - 1966 (Box 75)
  - Scrapbooks, 1966 (Box 81, Box 82)
    Box 81: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Scrapbook, 1967 (Box 84)
  - Metropolitan Dailies clippings, 1967 (Box 83)
  - Scrapbooks, 1968 (Box 87, Box 88, Box 89)
    Box 87: Scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Photographs of Mutuel Bays, 1968 (Box 86)
  - Advertising, 1968 - 1974 (Box 88)
    Hollywood Park generated advertisements which are not from newspapers; mostly glossy handbill-type items.
  - Scrapbook, 1969 (Box 90, Box 91)
  - Scrapbook, 1970 (Box 92, Box 93)
  - Scrapbook, 1971 (Box 94, Box 95, Box 96)
    Box 95: scrapbook contains photographs only.
  - Western Harness Racing, 1971-1974 (Box 102)
    Samples of admission tickets, parking service tickets, notices and other ticket- taking activity. Small number of Season Box holder lists, brochures and/or programs.
  - Scrapbooks, 1972 (Box 96, Box 97, Box 98, Box 333)
    Box 96: scrapbook contains photographs only. Box 98: Marineland clippings.
  - Scrapbooks, 1973 (Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 100)
    Box 99: Western Harness Publicity
  - Scrapbooks, 1974 (Box 101, Box 103, Box 104, Box 105)
    Box 105: Scrapbook contains photographs only. Box 103: Western Harness Publicity.
  - Scrapbooks, 1975 (Box 106, Box 107, Box 108)
    Box 106: Scrapbook contains photographs only. Box 108: Advertisements only. Box 107: Western Harness clippings.
  - Scrapbooks, 1976 (Box 109)
  - Golden Bear, 1976 (Box 111)
  - LA Times and Herald Examiner clippings, 1976 (Box 110)
  - Western Harness Racing newspaper clippings (1976); Wincorp Development newspaper clippings ('76 - '77); Wincorp Charity Foundation newspaper clippings (1977), 1976 - 1977 (Box 111)
  - Scrapbooks, 1977 (Box 113)
  - Hollywood Turf Club Inglewood, California: 38th Meeting, 1977 (Box 112)
  - WHR [Western Harness Racing] Newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 111)
  - Herald Examiner clippings, 1978 (Box 114)
  - Suburban Newspapers clippings, 1978 (Box 115)
  - WHR Newspaper clippings, 1978 (Box 114)
  - Santa Anita, 1979 (Box 116)
    Herald Examiner press.
  - Scrapbooks, 1979 (Box 117)
  - Western Harness Racing, 1979 Aug - Dec (Box 115)
  - Western Harness, 1980 (Box 118)
  - Scrapbooks, 1980 (Box 119)
  - Scrapbooks, 1980 - 1981 (Box 120)
  - Scrapbook, 1981 (Box 121)
    Advertisements only.
  - Scrapbooks, 1981 (Box 122)
  - Oak Tree Sports Pages, 1981 (Box 123)
    Press from Herald Examiner and Los Angeles Times.
  - Sports Pages, 1981 (Box 123)
    Press from L.A. Sentinel, Daily News, Fresno Telegraph, Daily Breeze, Star News, Calendar, The Register, and others.
  - Sports Pages, 1982 (Box 124)
    Press from Calendar, Daily Express. Daily News, L.A. Sentinel, San Gabriel Valley Tribune, Star News, and The Register.
  - Scrapbook, 1986 July - Oct (Box 124)
  - Los Alamitos Fall Harness Meet, 1986 - 1988 (Box 125)
  - Scrapbook, 1987 - 1989 (Box 126)
    Hollywood Park advertisements only.
  - Scrapbook, 1987 - 1990 (Box 126)
    Santa Anita race track advertisements.
  - Scrapbook, 1988 - 1989 (Box 128)
  - Scrapbook, 1991 (Box 128)
  - Scrapbooks, 1992 (Box 127)
  - Scrapbook, 1993 (Box 85)
    Newspaper advertisements.
- Negatives, (1975-1996)
  The negatives are arranged in a loose chronological order with some boxes further arranged into a loose alphabetical order by event or individual's or thoroughbred's name.
  The negatives series comprise black and white and color negatives documenting various Hollywood Park race and track activities. The bulk of the negatives represent races, titles, and club parties with a small number of the items representing the Los Alamitos race track. Additionally, there are a very small number of printed photographs.
  - Negatives (Box 334)
    With unidentified persons and places, Lucille Ball and Desi Arnaz, Jimmy Durante, Buddy Gil 'Baldwin Stakes', Early Pioneer (Hollywood Gold Cup), Gold Cup, Golden Pheasant, [Johnny] Longden, Off season: Plastic Lungs at Rancho Los Amigos, Rio Verde, Spastic Childrens Foundation, Sports Illustrated group picture, Swaps, Swaps statue at entrance of Park, Shoemaker, infield landscape, and horse races.
  - Photographs (Box 334)
    With goose girl, the infield at Hollywood Park, and photographs that came loose from scrapbooks.
  - Hollywood Park Race and Club Parties Color Negatives (1 of 3) (A-N)
  - Hollywood Park Race and Club Parties Color Negatives (2 of 3) (O-W, Hollywood Park Titles and Club Parties)
  - Hollywood Park Race and Club Parties Color Negatives (3 of 3) (Club Parties)
  - Negatives (Black and White) (1 of 2) (January -May 1976 and People 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 295)
  - Negatives (Black and White) (2 of 2) (Miscellaneous - Horses 1975), 1975-1976 (Box 296)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Club Parties, Titles Negatives (1 of 3) (A-H), 1976 (Box 197)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Club Parties, Titles Negatives (2 of 3) (I-Z), 1976 (Box 198)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Club Parties, Titles Negatives (3 of 3) (Titles and Club Parties), 1976 (Box 199)
    Titles and Club Parties.
  - Negatives (Black and White), 1976 May - Dec (Box 297)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 199)
    A-B.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 200)
    C-S.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 201)
    T-Z, Titles, and Club Parties.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 203)
    A-F.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 204)
    G-Z.
  - PR Negatives January - September 1977 (2 boxes) (Box 297, Box 298)
    Box 297: January-April 1977; Box 298: May-September 1977.
  - Hollywood Club PR Negatives (1 of 3), 1977-1983 (Box 207)
    A-E.
  - Hollywood Club PR Negatives (2 of 3), 1977-1983 (Box 208)
    E-R.
  - Hollywood Club PR Negatives (3 of 3), 1977-1983 (Box 209)
    S, V, and unidentified items.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 202)
    A-P.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 203)
    Q-Z.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 205)
    A-N.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 206)
    O-Z, Club Parties.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 207)
    Titles.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 299)
    July-December 1978 and January-December 1979.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 300)
    January-July 1978.
  - Hollywood Park Actions Negatives (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 209)
  - Hollywood Park Actions Negatives (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 210)
    N-Z.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 210)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 211)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Titles, and Club Parties Negatives (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 212)
    Club Parties and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Racing Negatives (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 212)
    A-C.
  - Hollywood Park Racing Negatives (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 213)
    D-T.
  - Hollywood Park Racing Negatives (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 214)
    U-Z, Club Parties, and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 214)
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 215)
    General note
    G-Z and Titles.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 301)
    February-April 1980.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 302)
    May-December 1981.
  - Hollywood Park Publicity Negatives (1 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 216)
    A-M.
  - Hollywood Park Publicity Negatives (2 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 217)